-- Usagi Drop Episode 09 --
Typhoon No. 13 continues to exhibit strong signs of force as it makes its way up north.
It struck the Southern Daitou Islands at 11:00 PM last night.
So far there have been no reports on how this will affect transportation.
Daikichi!
They said the bullet trains are pooping!
No, they said they're operating.
Pooping?
No, operating!
They were probably reporting that the
bullet trains are still operating normally.
They mean the trains are running as usual.
They're pooping!
Now I have to poop!
Geez...
As the typhoon alters its route towards the east,
it is expected to make landfall in the Toukai region this evening.
Did she say typhoon?
Don't worry, typhoons come every year.
Daikichi!
Is there no toilet paper?
I've got a huge one!
Bring a ruler!
I know boys will be boys, but still...
I feel sorry for her.
Presented by:
Taka Fansubs
I'm picking you up early today.
Okay.
Let's go, Kouki-kun.
Wasn't that awesome?
We're gonna be late.
See you!
If you've left enough space for small circles, you've written the character properly.
Alright?
Sensei, how much space should we leave?
Well...
How many centimeters? Or millimeters?
You don't have to actually draw the circles!
Okay!
Okay, finish the rest for homework.
Next, all the first graders will have art class.
Gather in front of each of your morning glories.
Understood?
Yeah!
Who knew sandbags were that heavy?!
It's still morning and I'm already worn out.
It's just our luck all those samples had to go out today.
Thank you.
What's that?
It's my kids' educational endowment insurance.
What?! Aren't your kids still babies?
I can't wait until they're older to get insurance.
Oh, right.
I'm on that plan too.
Although I don't think any kid of mine dreams of college.
Money's tight since we have two kids.
Ours is still just a baby, but even
daycare costs are crazy these days.
Plus he grows out of his clothes constantly.
We may not be full-time employees here,
but it's nice they give us a welfare pension and health insurance.
What about life insurance?
My wife handled all that.
If I go under, she gets a decent sum,
but she's just on a savings coverage.
She says it's standard...
You guys really seem like dads.
Good for you.
It's not that big of a deal.
I wonder how much insurance costs?
We've been meaning to move away from the noisy kid next door, but we don't have the money to.
I don't even know what I'm working for anymore.
You better be listening to us!
This is what happens when you get married!
I don't even have a girlfriend, so no problem.
They may complain a lot,
but they really do care.
I can't see them turning into someone like Rin's mother.
Kouki-san!
Sit down and draw!
Run!
And where is your drawing board?
I don't need it, the ground's smooth.
Don't pull one on me!
Bring something when I tell you to bring it!
Run and go get it!
You're really good at drawing, Rin-chan!
She's right! It's really pretty!
It is?
You really are good!
The colors of these two flowers are different,
and you did a great job of drawing them blue and purple.
You have a knack for this!
Kouki-kun and those boys are goofing off again!
Kouki-san.
We're having art class now.
Your morning glories look great, Kouki-san!
They deserve to be drawn!
Do you like drawing?
Sort of, I guess.
Tatsumi-sensei, I'm in charge of this boy.
Kouki-san, why are you always stirring up trouble?!
Sit down and draw!
And don't make any faces!
We got Kouki's cap!
Give it back!
Hey, you boys! Stop that!
Come back here!
We got it! It's ours!
Rin-chan?
Kouki-kun, just sit down and draw!
Don't let them taunt you!
Okay.
You're really brave, Rin-chan.
Kouki-kun's always acting weird, and it's scary when he gets mad.
He's going to pick on you!
No, he won't!
We went to the same daycare.
What?
Really?
They're late.
You guys pick your kids up at six too, right?
Yeah, it'll be close today.
They're here!
Alright, let's do this in one trip.
Yeah!
Good evening.
A little wet, aren't you?
Rin-chan, your dad's here!
Hey!
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
I'll go get her.
It's pretty windy out there, isn't it?
Yeah. I would have liked to get here earlier.
Am I the last one?
Kouki-kun's still here.
Daikichi!
You see the storm?
Yup, it's wild outside.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
There's an umbrella flying!
Did something happen?
No, I'm fine.
See you!
See you later, Kouki!
Wanna come home with us?
Okay!
I'm sorry, but we can't let him go home with someone else.
I understand.
But the weather's only going to get worse later on,
so if it's not a problem I'll call Nitani-san.
I'll let you speak to her as well to confirm.
Well, in that case...
We'll be able to go home early too!
Hey!
We're just kidding.
Kouki!
I want to too!
Rin!
Be careful!
Follow after me!
Stop right there!
I'll get you a towel.
Oh, the storm shutters!
Awesome! Let me try!
Alright, just watch your hands.
It's so dark!
It's like a secret fort in here!
Ow, it got in my eyes!
Keep your eyes shut so I can wash it out.
Alright, dry yourself now.
Your back is huge, Daikichi!
Right?!
Good evening, it's Nitani.
I'm coming!
Kaga Rin
Daikichi
Daikichi's meat and potato
stew is really delicious.
And he can run really fast.
So I guess you were able to leave work early.
Sorry for taking matters into my own hands.
No, please! You really helped me out.
I'm sorry I got Kouki dripping wet too.
Please, I can't thank you enough.
It fits you perfectly!
Daikichi, let me have some of your clothes!
I told you to say "Daikichi-san"!
He said just "Daikichi" is fine!
I feel better when he just calls me that.
Yeah! Calling him "Daikichi" is fine!
You're really good at that, Rin-chan!
I know how to use a knife too!
Wow, you're like a young lady!
Daikichi uses the stove though.
I'll help!
But you never help out.
I'll help cut too!
You can use my knife!
Ow! I hate onions!
Don't touch your eyes! Go wash them right now.
Now I'm crying!
Where are you going?
Making hamburger patties?
Yup.
Looks good, doesn't it?
These don't look right.
They're fine! Right?
Well, they should taste fine.
Rin-chan, the eggs are done boiling!
Please peel them!
Okay!
Here!
You're amazing!
Rin's in her element.
Kouki, do you love your mom?
Maybe if she wasn't such a nagging old lady.
They really care for each other too.
I call this one!
You didn't give thanks for the meal!
Thanks for this meal!
Thank you for this meal.
Kouki, use your chopsticks.
I'm just moving it together.
Isn't it yummy?
Food really does taste better when we're all together!
Let's eat here again tomorrow!
Kouki!
Don't worry about the rest, I'll finish them later.
Okay.
And then it fell right on his head!
He's so happy.
I was never able to give him this kind of chance.
This evening really was great.
Thank you so much.
Please! I should be thanking you.
Sensei said not to draw the circles!
I'm glad I got to leave work early so I could see him smiling like that.
She's raising a child all alone as well.
Daikichi, come over here!
Coming.
I think we should go home now.
Should I call a taxi?
Yes, please.
Will you stay over?!
Rin!
Well, Reina-chan and her mom did!
That was different!
Later.
See you.
Bye-bye!
Thank you, Rin-chan.
And thank you for everything.
We had fun too.
Right?
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
The typhoon's gone?
Yup.
Rin-chan! Rin-chan!
Kouki-kun's here already?
He's early again!
Come in!
Are you sure?
No, wait!
I wanted to open up the storm shutters.
The sky's all clear!
We're leaving!
Kouki-kun, we're gonna be late.
See you.